Senior IT Engineer ROBERT SMITH

Phone: (123) 456 78 99 Email: info@qwikresume.com Website: www.qwikresume.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/qwikresume Address: 1737 Marshville Road,

labama.

Objective

Highly motivated software engineer with expertise in Application development and Embedded Systems Firmware development in various industries including Automotive, Railways, Energy and Telecommunications industries. With more than 10 years of experience in software design, development and testing, looking for an exciting career wherein can utilize skills in C/C++/Python/Ruby/Perl,Unix,Linux & embedded systems.

Skills

JIRA, LoadRunner, ITKO LISA, Web Services, Performance Testing, Identity Access Management, Oracle Identity Management, HP SiteScope, SOAP UI, Oracle SQL, Softerra, API Testing.

Work Experience

Senior IT Engineer

ABC Corporation - January 2008 - February 2013

- Provided other applications with the information about the simulated trains and the state of the tracks, GatewayTB implements the TCP/IP server.
- Used of such protocol allows any internet browser to act as a client for GatewayTB and get and display the data from it.
- Data received is in the Html and XML formats and shall be parsed.
- Involved in Requirement study of the Gateway TB HTTP server protocol for Communication Based Train Control simulator.
- Involved in the Documentation of Software Requirements & Documentation.
- Provided troubleshooting and on-call support for production environments.
- Responsible for leading cross-functional IT projects to customers such as Supply Chain, R&D, Marketing, Finance, or to entire company.

Senior IT Engineer

Delta Corporation - 2006 - 2008

- Supported seven J2EE environments including applications deployments, installation and configuration of WebSphere, WebLogic application servers and .
- Responsible for analyzing business requirements, creation of documentation and testing and maintenance of applications, infrastructure and .
- Project Management Delivered 955 servers with 9.5 TB storage across 4 data centers, which enabled key Connected-Print (ePrint) product launch with .
- Worked as a Senior Analyst in Deloitte Hyderabad from May 2011 to August 17th 2012.
- Worked as a Senior Software Engineer in Applabs Technologies (A CSC Company) Hyderabad from June 2010 to May 2011.
- Worked as a Performance Test Engineer in FAIR ISAAC (FICO) India Software Pvt.
- This is Dummy Description data, Replace with job description relevant to your current role.

Education
Bachelor of Engineering in Electronics & Dommunication - (Easwari Engineering College)